<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WeaponZ</string>

    <string name="rifles">Rifles are firearms designed for precision shooting, with a long barrel
        that has spiral grooves, known as rifling. This design causes the bullet to spin,
        stabilizing its flight and increasing accuracy over long distances.
        Rifles can be single-shot or capable of firing multiple rounds semi-automatically
        or fully automatically. They are commonly used in hunting, sports shooting, and by
        military and law enforcement agencies. Examples include the AK-47, known for its durability
        and use in various conflicts, and the M16, standard issue in many military forces.</string>

    <string name="snipers">Snipers are highly trained marksmen who use sniper rifles to engage targets
        from long distances, often beyond the target\'s awareness. They specialize in stealth,
        camouflage, and precision shooting, often providing critical reconnaissance for military
        operations. Sniper rifles are equipped with high-magnification scopes and are designed
        for extreme accuracy. The AWP (Arctic Warfare Police) and SCAR 20 are known for their
        accuracy and are used in military and law enforcement.</string>

    <string name="guns">The term "guns" encompasses a wide range of firearms, from small handguns
        to large artillery pieces. They operate by propelling projectiles through a metal tube using
        explosive force. Guns are used for personal defense, law enforcement, and warfare. Handguns
        like the Desert Eagle is a powerful handgun known for its stopping power, while the Five Seven
        is praised for its lightweight design and armor-piercing capabilities.</string>

    <string name="knives">Knives are tools with a cutting edge blade fixed to a handle, used for
        various purposes including cooking, crafting, and as weapons. They range from simple pocket
        knives to specialized combat knives. Examples include the pocket knife, convenient for everyday
        carry, and the hunting knife, designed for processing game in the field.</string>

    <string name="selfdefense">Self-defense weapons are designed to protect individuals from harm.
        They can be non-lethal, like pepper spray and stun guns, which incapacitate attackers
        temporarily, or lethal, like firearms. Examples include brass knuckles, which can be worn to
        increase the force of a punch, and stun guns, which deliver an electric shock to incapacitate
        an attacker.</string>

    <string name="home">Thank you for choosing and using our application. We are very happy to provide
        you our good info about every type of weapons.If you have any question, please reach to the
        main creator of this app which is me. Enjoy my app</string>
</resources>
